midwestern.edu 2019-10-28

# Privacy Policy - Midwestern University

This privacy policy covers Midwestern University's use and handling of information, including personally identifiable information, that we collect when you use this website. This privacy policy cannot and does not cover the practices of companies we do not own or control, or people we do not employ or manage.

Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site. We strive to collect, store and use the minimum amount of personal information that is necessary for our legitimate business purposes, and to comply with applicable legal obligations.

We may collect both non-personally identifiable and personally identifiable information when you visit or use our website. For example, we automatically receive and record non-personally identifiable information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested, as well as the page you linked from. We may set and access cookies on your computer. We also receive and record any personally identifiable information (including, for example, zip code, age, name, and e-mail address) you submit via forms on our website and correlate and analyze that information with commercially available databases when appropriate.

We may use information collected from you for four general purposes:

  * To monitor and improve performance of our website and generate aggregate statistical reports;
  * To customize the content you see when you visit our website; 
  * To fulfill your requests for certain services and information; and 
  * To contact you. In addition, we use tools such as Google Ads to remarket to individuals who visit our program pages.

Third-party vendors, such as Google, show our ads on sites across the internet, and in some cases, use cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website. Any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google's privacy policy.  You can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's [Ad Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). You can also opt out of all third-party vendors' use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**_We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone._**

## Contact

Midwestern University   
Office of Communications   
555 31st Street   
Downers Grove, IL 60515   
630/969-4400 phone  
630/515-7180 fax  

**This revision to our privacy policy is effective November 7, 2018. We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time by posting a modified version on this website, without providing any further notice.**
